She sold happiness in glass jars. The poster read, Happiness. Sold in glass jars.
Call today, and underneath the text was a phone number.
I was walking home from a long, exhausting day of work when I caught a glimpse of the
paper stapled on an old telephone pole. I took a picture of it thinking it was amusing.
I was going to show my wife once I got to her apartment, but I was caught up with chores and
forgot about it. Dinner, dishes, laundry, packing a snack for her daughter, putting her to bed,
then putting her toys away that she'd left out in the living room. Every night, it was the exact
same routine. The next day, I awoke sleeping back to back with my wife. I always had to get up
earlier than she did for my job, so I quietly got ready for the day and headed out the door.
At work, I was updating the company's latest expense report. Most days were similar to this
one. They were basically paying me to stare at a computer for nine hours a day and input a couple
numbers into a spreadsheet. I finished my work very quickly, so I decided to head out of the
office early. It also helped that it was a Friday and a lot of people leave early at the end of the
week. On my walk back, I was thinking of what my life had become. I did this often. I always
dreamed of traveling when I was younger. I wanted to drive across the country or solo backpack
across Europe. Then I met Kelsey. Don't get me wrong, I loved Kelsey. I mean, I still do. We
just don't have that spark anymore. When you meet someone and get in a relationship, whether it's
meant to be or not, some of your personal life plans have to be put on hold. And then that
relationship turns to marriage, and then you have a baby, then you have to enroll your daughter in a
preschool, then you have to get a better paying job and work more hours and blah, blah, blah.
I'm not trying to throw a pity party for myself. I'm just saying I wasn't exactly content with
where I was in my life. I wouldn't have referred to myself as a happy person, as I took the same
route home that I did every day to work and back, I walked by the same poster I had passed the day
before. I don't know why, I really don't, but I decided to call the number. I figured it would
be some joke. Maybe someone just picks up and says, I love you, on the other end and hangs up.
Or maybe it's a line to a sex worker. I had no idea what to expect. I called. It only rang once
before someone picked up. Hello? A woman said. Uh, hi, um, I'm calling about your poster? Your
ad? Oh, awesome, she said calmly. When do you want to pick it up? Pick what up? The jar, she said,
like it was the most obvious thing in the world. Oh, of course, um, I realized then that I had left
work early without telling Kelsey, so I could just go pick it up now and she'd be none the wiser.
What exactly is it? That you're selling? I just told you. It's happiness. In a glass jar. Like
the poster said, happiness keeps best in glass jars. They're more durable than, say, a plastic
bag. Um, okay, should we meet somewhere? For sure. I don't want you to end up being a creep or
something, so let's go to a public place. The public place we decided on was a Starbucks parking
lot a little over a mile from me. Now, I didn't think I was really going to be buying a jar of
happiness or whatever. I was 99% sure she was going to sell me drugs. Maybe heroin would be
in the jar. I remember thinking, oh no, happiness is probably a nickname for some street drug and
I'm going to a drug deal. What if she's a cop? Am I going to be arrested? But something inside me
told me to keep walking, and so I did. I stood outside and texted her. Me, I'm here. Her, cool,
be there in a sec. Me, what are you driving? Her, silver Camry. And as her final text came through,
I saw her car pull in. She took a spot not too far from where I stood. I could see there was no
one else in the car, which put my kidnapping fear to rest. She opened her door and stood on the
pavement, looking around until her eyes met mine. I gave her a little nod of acknowledgement. She
simply responded by waving her hand, gesturing for me to come over to her car, so I did.
She was young, maybe mid-twenties, with curly, golden hair. Her skin was pale and contrasted
with the all-black outfit she was wearing. I thought she looked like Glinda the Good Witch
from The Wizard of Oz had put on the Wicked Witch's clothes. Nice day out, she said as a
greeting.